<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <masterLabel>Consultation Prep Notes</masterLabel>
    <description>Generates structured consultation prep notes from a customer 360 profile. Used by Clientelling Copilot.</description>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>
You are generating structured consultation preparation notes for an in-store beauty rep about to start a face-to-face consultation.

CUSTOMER 360 PROFILE:
{!$Input:CustomerProfile}

APPOINTMENT TYPE:
{!$Input:AppointmentType}

STORE LOCATION:
{!$Input:StoreLocation}

---

Generate structured talking points organized by priority. Each point should be actionable — something the rep can say or reference during the consultation.

1. LOYALTY AND RELATIONSHIP STATUS
   - Tier, points balance, available rewards or vouchers
   - How long they have been a member
   - Example: &quot;Gold-tier member with 2,400 points — mention the new rewards catalog&quot;

2. RECENT PURCHASES AND RESTOCK OPPORTUNITIES
   - Products purchased in the last 90 days
   - Estimate restock timing based on product category (serums about 2 months, moisturizers about 3 months, sunscreen about 2 months)
   - Example: &quot;Last purchase: LUMIERE Night Serum (3 weeks ago) — ask how it is working&quot;

3. PREVIOUS CONSULTATION NOTES
   - Key observations from past consultations
   - Unresolved concerns or interests
   - Example: &quot;Previous consultation noted interest in anti-aging — the new Renewal Collection just launched&quot;

4. MEANINGFUL EVENTS AND LIFE CONTEXT
   - Upcoming events (weddings, travel, milestones)
   - Recent life changes that affect product needs
   - Example: &quot;Mentioned trip to Bali coming up — suggest travel-size SPF options&quot;

5. BROWSE AND ENGAGEMENT SIGNALS
   - Recent browsing categories (soft reference only — this is inferred data)
   - Example: &quot;Has been browsing anti-aging serums online recently&quot;

6. BEAUTY PROFILE AND PREFERENCES
   - Skin type, concerns, allergies
   - Brand preferences, sustainability preferences
   - Example: &quot;Sensitive skin, prefers clean beauty — lead with SERENE and BOTANICA&quot;

7. PRODUCT RECOMMENDATIONS (provenance-aware)
   - 3-5 specific products to discuss, aligned to their profile
   - For 3P-informed tier selections, frame as &quot;Staff picks&quot; not &quot;Based on profile&quot;
   - NEVER surface raw 3P appended data (household income, demographics)

OUTPUT:
Return a concise bulleted list of up to 10 actionable talking points. Start each with the section category in brackets, e.g. [Loyalty], [Restock], [Event], [Beauty Profile], [Staff Picks].
        </content>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>CustomerProfile</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Customer Profile</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:CustomerProfile</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>AppointmentType</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Appointment Type</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:AppointmentType</referenceName>
            <required>false</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>StoreLocation</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Store Location</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:StoreLocation</referenceName>
            <required>false</required>
        </inputs>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT4Omni</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
    </templateVersions>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
