<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <masterLabel>Scene Background Directive</masterLabel>
    <description>Generates dynamic scene backgrounds for the Beauty Concierge storefront. NOT used by Clientelling Copilot.</description>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>
You generate a sceneContext JSON object for a beauty storefront background image.

CONVERSATION CONTEXT:
{!$Input:ConversationContext}

PRODUCT IDs BEING DISPLAYED:
{!$Input:ProductIds}

CUSTOMER CONTEXT TAGS:
{!$Input:CustomerContextTags}

---

YOUR TASK: Return ONLY a JSON sceneContext object. Do NOT return a full uiDirective, do NOT include product data, do NOT include action fields. The calling agent will embed your sceneContext into its own uiDirective response.

SETTING: Pick the closest match from: &quot;neutral&quot;, &quot;bathroom&quot;, &quot;travel&quot;, &quot;outdoor&quot;, &quot;lifestyle&quot;, &quot;bedroom&quot;, &quot;vanity&quot;, &quot;gym&quot;, &quot;office&quot;. This is a fallback category for caching. If nothing fits, use &quot;neutral&quot;.

BACKGROUND PROMPT: Write a vivid 1-2 sentence scene description that matches the conversation context. Be creative and specific. Examples:
- &quot;Elegant marble bathroom counter with morning light streaming through frosted glass, fresh eucalyptus and white towels&quot;
- &quot;Busy New York City street at golden hour, urban chic, glass storefronts reflecting sunset&quot;
- &quot;Tropical beachside cabana at sunset, ocean breeze, palm fronds and coconut&quot;
- &quot;Cozy candlelit bedroom vanity with soft pink lighting and rose petals&quot;

GENERATE BACKGROUND: Set to true when the conversation implies a specific visual setting (destination, emotional mood, life event). Set to false for generic browsing or follow-up questions.

OUTPUT FORMAT — return exactly this JSON structure and nothing else:
{
  &quot;setting&quot;: &quot;travel&quot;,
  &quot;backgroundPrompt&quot;: &quot;Your vivid scene description here&quot;,
  &quot;generateBackground&quot;: true,
  &quot;customerContext&quot;: &quot;tags from input if available&quot;
}
        </content>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>ConversationContext</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Conversation Context</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:ConversationContext</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>ProductIds</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Product IDs</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:ProductIds</referenceName>
            <required>false</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>CustomerContextTags</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>Customer Context Tags</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:CustomerContextTags</referenceName>
            <required>false</required>
        </inputs>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT4Omni</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
    </templateVersions>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
